Parna Asadi

Front-end Engineer

≥ parna.asadi2001@gmail.com

+989379935851

• Tehran, Iran ## 09/09/2001

in parna-asadi (perriex

PROFILE

Solution-driven Front-end Developer adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS, Node, is and JavaScript. Built products for desktop and mobile app users over 3+ years, meeting highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices and speed. Designed and developed web applications across multiple APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Product Manager, Front-end Developer

2022 - present Toronto, Canada

Itica &

- Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.
- Coded using **React**, **SCSS** and **Next.js** to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.
- Mentored and guided employees to foster proper completion of assigned duties.
- Developed and published six websites (Rhythmitica
 Ø web and Dashboards, Behbood
 Ø web and Dashboards, LearnPersianArt &, Hoomankhalatbari & and Itica Kids &).

Full-stack Developer

06/2020 - 04/2023

Tehran, Iran

Rayan Afzar Forough - Kanoon Ghalamchi &

- Used **React**, **node.js** and **MongoDB** to develop app-solutions.
- Developed efficient websites according to business objectives and needs of clients.
- Consulted with engineering team members to determine system loads and develop improvement plans.
- Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.
- Mentored junior members and delivered training to boost team skills set.
- Updated old code bases to modern development standards, improving functionality.
- Developed and published four websites (Bartarha ∂ web and dashboards, Khayerin madreseh saz).

Front-end Developer

09/2022 - 02/2023 Texas, United States

PaperScore &

- Transformed React application into mobile-friendly Next.js website.
- Updated old code bases to modern development standards, improving functionality.
- Discussed issues with team members to provide resolution and apply best practices.

Front-end Developer

07/2022 - 09/2022

Tehran, Iran

Padidar net &

- Designed and updated layouts to meet usability and performance requirements.
- Coded using React, Styled Components and Axios to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.

EDUCATION

10/2019 - 08/2023Bachelor's degree

University of Tehran ≥ Computer Engineering, Software Engineering Tehran, Iran

PROJECTS

Hekidesk ∂ 08/2023 React, Bootstrap components, Canvas and BLE (Bluetooth Low Energy) Developing software application (web and native) to analyze health condition of patients. Improving performance and build Bluetooth-based application for transferring data from health device. **ProbStat** 01/2023 React and Tailwind.css Developed a user-friendly website for education and learning Probability and Statistics. JSON maker ∂ 08/2022 React and Typescript JSON to Web-page form and download filled form in JSON format, designed with Evergreen-ui components. EZjson ℰ is an experimental project. Persian Talent & 09/2022 Angular Developed Persian Talent with Angular-v12. Internship for Code Academy-2022. 08/2022 Spotify *⊘* Angular Developed an example of Spotify website using Angular. Internship for Code Academy-Alorotbeh ∂ 07/2021 React and Typescript Participated in the development of (alorotbe.com) ∅ using MUI-4 and Chart.js. **COURSES** 01/2023 - 07/2023**Internet Engineering** University of Tehran Tehran, Iran Teacher's assistant of this course, Teaching React, HTML5, CSS and Javascript. **ACM Code Academy** 07/2022 - 09/2022University of Tehran Tehran, Iran Mentored Front-end development course in Summer Camp of ACM. **LANGUAGES** Persian-Farsi English **SKILLS** React.js Angular CSS/SCSS **Typescript** node.js JavaScript Figma Product Manager **BLE** Scrum Master Trello DevOps Jira Bootstrap **Tailwindcss** Styled Components MongoDB My SQL/SQL C# .NET Php Java Mentoring Training Git Github Adobe XD Microsoft Project